# STEEV JOSE KUNDUKULANGARA

Bangalore, India ●sk@stevekundukulangara.com ● (91) 8149983249

#### **PROFILE SUMMARY**

I am a seasoned technical writer that transitioned from a system analyst role. As I was passionate about translating complex information to novice users, I decided to make this transition. The following experience provides a high-level overview of my contributions. I would be happy to elaborate on my achievements when we connect.

#### **EDUCATION**

# **Bachelor of Science, Information Technology**

May 2014

University of Mumbai

### **PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE**

## Perfios Software Solutions, Bangalore, India – Senior Technical Writer

Apr 2024- Present

- Migrated all API documents from Google docs to Open API specifications. (Achieved recognition from PM).
- Created a Product Site using Docusaurus for internal products from scratch.
- Created certification contents for product for internal team members. (Achieved recognition from PM).

# Accionlabs Pvt Ltd, Bangalore, India – Senior Technical Writer

May 2022- Mar 2024

- Created an internal knowledge base on Google sites for information search.
- Created user manuals, API documents, and worked with stakeholders to research and write white papers.

#### Westernlotto, Lagos, Nigeria – System Analyst

Dec 2018- Mar 2022

- Automated generation of Excel reports using Pandas library from Python significantly reducing manual effort and improving efficiency.
- Developed a custom program in Python to analyze and identify the most played numbers in the lottery to help mitigate risks and increase profitability by 20%.
- Created a support site in Wordpress to answer queries of the online betting customers.

### Dusane Infotech, Mumbai, India—Technical Support Engineer

Oct 2016 - Oct 2018

- Visited 3 different clients sites in Nigeria for product launch and training.
- Created user manuals and support sites for clients in Africa.

### IT Source Pvt Ltd, Mumbai, India – Technical Support Engineer

Jun 2015-Oct 2016

Served as primary point of contact for support relating to owned solutions and products

## **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

YAML | Markdown | HTML | Python | Git | SQL

## **TOOLS EXPERTISE**

Camtasia | Static Site Generators | OpenAPI | Confluence | Jira | Canva | Shotcut | DITA

### **HONORS & AWARDS**

#### Pat on the back

- Achieved for OpenAPI implementation and Swagger Bundling.
- Preparing Certification material for internal training.

### **PORTFOLIO**

- https://github.com/kstevejose
- https://kstevejose.hashnode.dev/